https://www.catfishedge.com/privacy-policy/

MenuHomeProductsAboutCatfish Guide ServiceBlogCatfish RigsCatfish BaitCatfishing TipsCatfishing GearCatfish BoatsTechniquesPodcastNewsVideosContact This Privacy Policy was last modified on September 22, 2017.Catfish Edge (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates https://www.catfishedge.com (the “Site”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at https://www.catfishedge.com.Information Collection And Use While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, postal address and phone number (“Personal Information”).Log Data Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.Cookies Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.Security The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Links To Other Sites Our Site may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.Catfish Edge has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party sites or services.Changes To This Privacy Policy Catfish Edge may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.Contact Us If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us. DisclosureThis blog is a sponsored blog created or supported by a company, organization or group of organizations. For questions about this blog, please contact chad@catfishedge.com.This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post may not always be identified as paid or sponsored content.The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.This blog does contain content which might present a conflict of interest. This content may not always be identified.Recent Posts The Best Catfish Rigs For Big Catfish Catfish Rods: The Ultimate Guide To Catfish Rods Catfish Rigs: The Best Rigs For Catfishing Best Catfish Bait: The Top 5 Catfish Baits Made Simple Catfish Species Essentials: The “Big Three” Types Of CatfishCategoriesCatfish BaitCatfish BoatsCatfish RigsCatfishing GearCatfishing TipsCatfishing VideosNewsPodcastTechniquesUncategorizedPagesHomeShopGuide ServiceAboutBlogContactProducts
Secret Catfish Rig [eBook] Rated 4.87 out of 5 $19.99
Catching Shad: How To Catch Shad [eBook] Rated 4.94 out of 5 $24.99
Summer Channel Catfish [eBook] Rated 4.68 out of 5 $57.00
Drift Fishing For Catfish [eBook] Rated 4.77 out of 5 $27.99
Catfish Edge Logo Decal Rated 5.00 out of 5 $3.95 – $5.95Site SearchCopyright 2019 - Catfish Edge
Find Us On - Instagram, Twitter, Facebookand Google+,
Privacy Policy   Terms Of ServiceSearch
